TONNY ANDRIAMBOLOLONA

WEB DEVELOPER / DESIGNER

PROFILE

With almost 2 years of experience in web development, both within corporate environments and as a freelancer, I am actively seeking new professional challenges. I aim to apply my skills and fuel my passion for continuous learning.

CONTACT

- +1 438 722 6839
- tonny.mtl@gmail.com
- https://444tonny.github.io/Portfolio/

EDUCATION

IT University Madagascar

2018 - 2022

Bachelor's degree in web development & Design

ESIDEM Montréal, Canada

2023

DEP in IT Support

SOFT SKILLS

- Creative with a sense of aesthetics
- Team player
- Curiosity and adaptability
- Effective time management
- Detail-oriented

LANGUAGES

French: Native
English: Advanced

SKILLS

- UI/UX & Web Design
 - Figma, Adobe Photoshop & XD
 - HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, Responsive design, jQuery & Ajax
- Full Stack Development
 - PHP, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#
 - Frameworks: Laravel, CodeIgniter, VueJS, AngularJS
 - CMS: WordPress
 - Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Migration, Deployment, Web Administration
 - o Github, GitLab, Linux CLI

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lifetime Travel Madagascar (Nov 2021 - Mar 2022)

Designer / Full Stack developer

- Designed Logo + UI/UX + Database structure.
- Development of client and administrator website.
- Technical support for employees.

Kaki Agency (Mar 2022 - May 2022)

Web Integrator

- Integration of mockups on WordPress.

Upwork (since June 2022)

Designer / Front-end / Full Stack developer

- Designing & developing +5 websites for various clients as a freelance .
- Debugging, Optimization, SEO, Maintenance and deployment of websites.